{
    "id": "c6c4517765c249b68d1337f9167c42ed",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The three brothers love ………………………….",
            "description": "Each other refers to two people one another refers to more than two people.",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a260e0fa5124213bdc25801b1fefc44"
        },
        {
            "question": "The husband and the wife should love and respect ………………………….",
            "description": "Each other refers to two people one another refers to more than two people.",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29ebfe948acb445099121ff0aa36e633"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let …………………………… go now.",
            "description": "Let is a verb. A pronoun used as the object of a verb should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8eda0f6c279a4941938c1d232891edfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not as intelligent as ……………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are common after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "660a6d24d9284139a4acf321994bc987"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither answer ………………………….. correct.",
            "description": "We use a singular verb after either and neither. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34beff90f1a04fdf8061786bc54531ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is smarter than …………………………….",
            "description": "Object pronouns are common after than. Subject pronouns are also possible with a verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "I am",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e31bfdbe8251411ba2152215ebe5657e"
        },
        {
            "question": "People suffer when ………………………….. do not have money.",
            "description": "We use they to refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "we",
                "they"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b032d8705dac41edaab54e04089e2213"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy …………………………….. of movies.",
            "description": "Use this with kind and these with kinds.",
            "answers": [
                "this kind",
                "these kinds",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "905ff4c423b947e2a640e22f28c9dab7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not trust these ………………………….. of people",
            "description": "Use kinds and sorts with these and those.",
            "answers": [
                "kind",
                "kinds",
                "sorts"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2099b18393fa4c1cbda2f5479fc46937"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. a rainy day, we stayed inside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "It being"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9ae141e90fc542919e57ab2ad5184024"
        },
        {
            "question": "My essay is better than ………………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my friend",
                "that of my friend",
                "my friends",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25da6fde4afa495bbec9e1975f4f51d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my car. Is that ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "825533c425d34640aafdab3dd7808073"
        }
    ]
}